http://www.midlife-career-change.com/privacy-policy/

Your Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we
provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the
choices you can make about the way your information is collected and
used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our
homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information
may be requested.
Google AdSense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve
ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to
serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website
as well as other sites on the Internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL, http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to
track user’s activities on this website to measure advertisement
effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own
privacy policies. We have no access or control over these cookies that
may be used by third party advertisers.
Collection of Personal Information
When visiting this website website, the IP address used to access the
site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This
information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track
user’s movement and gather broad demographic information for internal
use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to
personally identifiable information.
Links to third party Websites
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We
are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You
should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from
our own.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our
discretion. If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy,
then please contact us.
